Hi, this is Rich Buccola here in NYC.
I like to let my chicken settle because what happens is if you cut it right away all the juice will fall out.
If you let it sit, the juices tend to stay in.
This is also a good time to preheat your oven to 400 degrees.
I just laid my chicken out like this and I'll just cut it in like quarter inch pieces like so and we're just going to get nice bite size cubes.
So we're just going to cut it like across and then you turn your chicken this way again just quarter inch just make little bite size pieces.
I'm just putting some chicken on top of chicken just to make it a little easier cutting three pieces at a time.
What you're going to do is just cut it one way turn it like so and cut these into bite size pieces .
So we have all our pieces in bite size.
What is great about these cutting boards is just pick it up put it right into our bowl.
But also at this point I'm going to add a little bit more salt going around a couple of times and some more fresh pepper, we're going to mix all this thoroughly through.
It's coming together.
We are going to start now with our phyllo bread and we're going to add a little parsley to this too.